<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="my_difficult_ans">
        <item>Content provider are the only way to share data accros Android Application, They store and retrieve data
        thus making it accessible to all </item>

        <item>Any kind of disturbence in Android operating system, System generate a broadcast message in all the apps,
        problems like received message , battery low
        These types of message from os received by BroadCast Receivers</item>

        <item>Android includes a set of core libraries that provides most of the functionality available in the core libraries of the
            Java programming language. Every Android application runs in its own process, with its own instance of the Dalvik virtual machine.
            Dalvik has been written so that a device can run multiple VMs efficiently. The Dalvik VM executes files in the Dalvik Executable
            (.dex) format which is optimized for minimal memory footprint. The VM is register-based, and runs classes compiled by a Java
            language compiler that have been transformed into the .dex format by the included dx tool</item>


        <item>The OHA is a consortium of 84 technology and mobile companies that have joined hands to accelerate innovation in mobile
            technology and at the same time offer the end users a better, cost-effective and richer mobile experience. Members of this
            include Google, HTC, Sony, Dell, Intel, Motorola, Qualcomm, Texas Instruments, Samsung, LG, T-Mobile, Nvidia. The OHA was
            started on 5 November 2007 by Google and 34 other companies. Android is the main software of the alliance. </item>

        <item>A ViewGroup is a special view that can contain other views (called children.) The view group is the base class for layouts and views containers.
            This class also defines the class ViewGroup.LayoutParams which serves as the base class for layouts parameters. </item>

        <item>Service is like an Activity but has no interface. Probably if you want to fetch the weather for example you would not create a
            blank activity for it, for this you will use a Service. It is also known as Background Service because it performs tasks in
            background. A Thread is a concurrent unit of execution. You need to know that you cannot update UI from a Thread.
            You need to use a Handler for this. </item>


  <item>A Status Bar Notification: It is used for persistent reminders that come from the background and request the users response.
A Dialog Notification: It is Used for Activity-related notifications.</item>

 <item>The use of XML-based layouts provides a consistent and somewhat standard means of setting GUI definition format. In common
     practice, layout details are placed in XML files while other items are placed in source files. </item>

<item>Containers, as the name itself implies, holds objects and widgets together, depending on which specific items are needed and in
    what particular arrangement that is wanted. Containers may hold labels, fields, buttons, or even child containers, as examples</item>


        <item>Orientation, which can be set using setOrientation(), dictates if the LinearLayout is represented as a row or as a column.
            Values are set as either HORIZONTAL or VERTICAL. </item>



    </string-array>

</resources>