<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

   <string-array name="my_simple_ans">
       <item>Android is a stack of software for mobile device, which includes a operating system and middleware and some key application
        Application executes with its own process and own instance that is DVM device</item>

        <item>The Google Android SDK is a toolset that developers need in order to write apps on Android enabled device. it
        contains many tools</item>

        <item>Android Architecture is made up 4 key components

        1 Linus kernal
        2 Libraries
        3 Android Framework
        4 Android Applications</item>

       <item>AAPT stands for Android asset packaging tools this tool is used to construct the distributable Android package files(.apk)</item>

        <item> The Intent is Simple message object, that is used to communicate between android components such as activity
        , content providers, broadcast receivers and services</item>

        <item>Intent - The Intent is Simple message object, that is used to communicate between android components such as activity
         content providers, broadcast receivers and services

            Services- A service is a component that runs in the background to perform long running operation or to perform
        work for remote processes, A Service does not provide user interface</item>

       <item>The (Android Packaging Key) APK file is compressed format of the AndroidManifest.xml file, application code (.dex files), resource files, and other files. A project is compiled into a single .apk file. </item>

       <item>As an activity transitions from state to state, it is notified of the change by calls to the following protected methods:
1) void onCreate(Bundle savedInstanceState)
2) void onStart()
3) void onRestart()
4) void onResume()
5) void onPause()
6) void onStop()
       7) void onDestroy()
Taken together, these seven methods define the entire lifecycle of an activity. </item>


       <item>Android applications are written using the Java programming language</item>
       <item>Android programs are compiled into .dex (Dalvik Executable) files, which are in turn zipped into a single .apk file on the device. .dex files can be created by automatically, translating compiled applications written in the Java programming language.
       </item>

   </string-array>
</resources>